

Robert Mendoza

JR. Front-End Developer | JavasScript | React Js | NodeJs

CONTACT

+549 11 2388 8420



⊠ Robmr.dev@gmail.com



Argentina, CABA



in linkedin.com/in/ramr-dev/

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Bilingual (C1)

Portuguese: Basic

APTITUDES

- Analytical capacity
- **Bug Resolution**
- Interface design
- Task planning
- Continuous improvement
- Effective communication

SKILLS

- Landing page design
- E-commerce development
- Rest API handling
- AGILE methodology

OTHER INTERESTS

- Storytelling
- **Digital Marketing**
- GitHub

ABOUT ME

More Info,



Professional in Commercial Management with years of experience in the automotive sector.

Currently interested in the development of applications using the knowledge acquired in recent years such as; SASS, Bootstrap, GSAPt; Vite, Git, Github.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer Jr | FreeLance

Argentina, | 2022 - Present

- Development of responsive web pages.
- Visual customization of web pages.
- Adaptation of old designs to modern sites.
- Product management using databases for easier implementation on the Front-End.

Commercial Advisor | CyclesMotoshop

Argentina, CABA, | 2021-2023

- Sales management.
- Manage tasks and objectives of Sales, administration and workshop.
- Responsible for help desk and customer-staff satisfaction indicators

Commercial Advisor | Unomotos

Argentina, Caba | 2018 – 2021

- Sales location manager.
- Sales management and advice to end clients.
- Structuring payment and tax plans adapted to the client's specific needs.

EDUCATION

Front-End React Development Career

Coderhouse, Argentina | 2022 - 2023

Includes web design technologies, Javascript and Reat Js

Bachelor's degree in Science. Biology

Universidad de los Andes, Venezuela | 2008 - 2014